https://www.stjames-parish.com/privacy-policy/

Adult
G.I.F.T.
Glafcke Family Mission
Laudato Si’
Adult
G.I.F.T.
Glafcke Family Mission
Laudato Si’
Updated: August 24, 2018
Welcome to the website (the “Website”) of St. James Church, Menomonee Falls.  This Website is operated by St. James Church (the “Church”). This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) states St. James Church’s policy relative to the information, including personal data and other information, collected from visitors to this Website.
Information Collected
When you visit St. James Church using this Website, the Church may collect personal data from you.  The data collected includes the following:
Personal Information.  The Church only collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis.  This information is provided to the Church by the visitor through the completion and submission of forms, inquiries, and other similar means.  “Personal Information” may include, but is not limited to, a visitor’s name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. By voluntarily providing the Church with Personal Information, the provision of such information indicates the visitor’s consent to the Church’s use of the Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.
Non-Personal Information.  When you interact with the Church via this Website, the Church receives and stores certain personally non-identifiable information (“Non-Personal Information”).  Non-Personal Information, which is passively collected using various technologies, cannot be used to identify a specific user.  The Church may store such information itself or in databases owned and maintained by Church affiliates, agents, or service providers.  The Church may aggregate personally non-identifiable information.
Cookies. In connection with the operation of this Website, the Church may employ the use of technology commonly known as “cookies.”  A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to the Internet browser of a visitor to that website.  A “cookie” is not a computer program and has no ability to read data residing on the visitor’s computer or instruct it to perform any step or function.  The “cookie” does not extract any Personal Information.
Use of Information Collected
The Church uses Personal Information a visitor provides in a manner consistent with this Policy.  If a visitor provides Personal Information for a specific reason, the Church will use the Personal Information for the purpose it was provided.  The Church, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and agents may use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information collected through the Website to improve the content and functionality of the Website.
The Church may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect or defend the rights or property of the Church (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of visitors to the Website, or (iv) protect against legal liability.
Disclosure of Information Collected
The Church will not sell, license, transmit, or disclose information collected to parties unaffiliated with the Church unless such sale, license, transmittal, or disclosure is expressly authorized by the visitor or required or permitted by law.  In all cases, the Church will disclose information collected consistent with applicable laws and regulations, and will require the recipient of such information to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.
Exclusions
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information collected by the Church other than Personal Information collected through this Website.  The Church shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute any unsolicited information to others without limitation or attribution. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Website, such as bulletin boards, any ideas for new information, resources, products or services, and other unsolicited submissions.
Use by Children
The Church does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through this Website. If there is reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information through this Website, please contact the Church.
Security
The Church takes reasonable precautions to protect visitors to its Website and information provided by such visitors.  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. The Church is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.
Hyperlinks to Other Websites
This Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites not operated or controlled by the Church   (“Third Party Websites”).  The Churchis not responsible for either the privacy policies of Third Party Websites or the validity of information contained therein.  Inclusion of hyperlinks to Third Party Websites does not in any manner imply any endorsement of the material on Third Party Websites or association with their owners or operators.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES
YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. THE CHURCH EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES REGARDING DATA PRIVACY OR DATA SECURITY.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT THE CHURCH SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.  YOU SPECIFICALLY AGREE THAT THE CHURCHIS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY VIOLATION OF THE RIGHTS OF ANY PARTY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, RIGHTS OF PUBLICITY, OR RIGHTS OF PRIVACY. IF THE CHURCH IS FOUND TO HAVE VIOLATED ANY OF YOUR RIGHTS, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY DAMAGES RECOVERABLE AGAINST THE CHURCH ARE LIMITED TO THE LESSER OF YOUR ACTUAL, PROVEN DAMAGES OR $10.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
All matters relating to the Website and this Policy and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims), shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Wisconsin without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule.
Any legal suit, action or proceeding arising out of, or related to, these Terms of Use or the Website shall be instituted exclusively in the federal courts of the United States or the courts of the State of Wisconsin, in each case located in the Village of Menomonee Falls and County of Waukesha.
Changes to Privacy Policy
The Church reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice by posting the updated Privacy Policy on this page.  Continued use of this Website after updates have been posted shall indicate agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.
Contact Information
To offer comments about this Website or about the information present in this Privacy Policy, please contact the Church at:
Search for:
W220 N6588 Town Line Rd.
Menomonee Falls, WI 53051
(262) 251-3944 (Parish Office)
(262) 251-0897 (Christian Formation)
stjameschurch@bizwi.rr.com
Mass Times
Mass Times
Please follow CDC guidelines.
Please follow instructions from ushers.
St. James -  Saturday 4:30 pm - Sunday 8:15 & 10:30 am
Good Shepherd - Saturday 4:30 pm - Sunday 9:30 am
Serving the Suburbs West of Milwaukee
St. James is a Catholic church in the Archdiocese of Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
G.I.F.T.
Laudato Si’
Knights of Columbus (KC’s)
Volunteer Opportunities
Close
